[{"question": " so i told carl, \u0091nobody, no matter how famous their parents are, nobody is allowed to climb on the dinosaur.\u0092 but of course this went in one ear and out.....", "answer": " i love how he cares so much about stuff. if i squint i can pretend he\u0092s alan alda.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh good, another dinosaur story. when are those gonna become extinct?", "answer": " if i was a superhero who could fly and be invisible, that would be the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hey. when you guys were kids and you played happy days, who were you? i was always richie.", "answer": " i was always joanne.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " ewww! oh! it\u0092s the mattress king!", "answer": " booo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  don\u0092t look honey. change the channel! change the channel!", "answer": " wait! wait! i wanna see this. after i divorce him, half of that kingdom is gonna be mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  \u0091despair fills the mattress showroom. my kingdom is suddenly without a queen. i\u0092m so depressed i\u0092m going to slash... my prices!! check it out! four ninety-nine for a pillow top queen set! i\u0092m going medieval on prices!", "answer": " what a wank!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " oh, i cannot believe he\u0092s using our divorce to sell mattresses.", "answer": " i know! and four ninety-nine for a pillow top queen set, who cares about the divorce, those babies will sell themselves.  and i\u0092m appalled for you by the way.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " we?", "answer": " are ah, having dinner with my dad tomorrow night, i hope that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh shoot, tomorrow\u0092s not so good, i\u0092m supposed to um, fall off the empire state building and land on a bicycle with no seat. sorry.", "answer": " ross, my father doesn\u0092t hate you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " please, he refers to me as \u0091wethead\u0092.", "answer": " but honey he calls everybody by a nickname! okay, look, i know, all right, just one dinner, please, just one night for me, please. i just want him to love you like i do.  all right, well not exactly like i do, but, but, if you do come to dinner, i\u0092ll love you like i do in that black thing that you like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  i\u0092ll go.", "answer": " fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " hi gunther.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " yeah, we\u0092ll see!", "answer": "  hey, you guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " guess what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i got a gig!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yay!!", "answer": " see, that\u0092s why i could never be an actor. because i can\u0092t say gig.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " yeah, i can\u0092t say croissant.  oh my god!", "answer": " what\u0092s the part?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, it\u0092s not a part, no. i\u0092m teaching acting for soap operas down at the learning extension.", "answer": " come on! that\u0092s great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " yeah, yeah. it\u0092s like my chance to give something back to the acting community.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " y\u0092know your probably not allowed to sleep with any of your students.", "answer": "  i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " ugh! i don\u0092t know monica. it feels funny just being here. i mean if you buy a bed from janice\u0092s ex-husband, that\u0092s like betraying chandler.", "answer": " not at these prices.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "   hi. y'know in england this car would be on the other side of the store.  woo!", "answer": "  oh! ohhhhh! oh! phoebe, come here. aw, this is my new bed. you gotta feel this bad boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey! ooh! how was teaching last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh it was great. yeah, you get to say stuff like, \u0092hey, the bell doesn\u0092t dismiss you, i dismiss you.\u0092", "answer": " ooooh, nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, and guess what, i got an audition for all my children.", "answer": " oh, yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " dom da-da dom! here ye! here ye! delivery from the mattress king.  you miss geller?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey, monica bought a bed from the mattress king?", "answer": " yeah, so please, please, please, don\u0092t say anything to chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " you want me to lie to chandler?", "answer": " is that a problem?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " oh, hey, hey nick the boxer let\u0092s see what you got. all right ya, put \u0091em up. come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hey, you\u0092re ah, pretty good at this.", "answer": " yeah, well i had to learn, i was staying at the y and some off the young men weren\u0092t acting christian enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " hey!!! oww!! and i\u0092m bleeding.", "answer": " oh! oh! oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " okay, great.", "answer": " wow! and i\u0092m a vegetarian! all right, all right, well i\u0092m sorry, we\u0092ll put some ice on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " \u0091kay, put your head back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " all right. i can\u0092t see.", "answer": " all right, i have ya. oh god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " which bedroom do ya want it in miss geller?", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s the compulsively neat one by the window, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " hi daddy!", "answer": " this where they put it? what, there no table available in the kitchen! hello, baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " you remember ross.", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " nice to see you again dr. green.", "answer": " so!   how\u0092s the library?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " ugh, museum.", "answer": " what happened to the library?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " there never was a library. i mean there are libraries, its just that i ah, i never worked at one.", "answer": " you know what\u0092s really good here, the lobster. what do you say shall i just order three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " yeah, if you\u0092re really hungry.  it was a joke, i made a joke.", "answer": " yeah, actually daddy ross is allergic to lobster.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what kind of person is allergic to lobster? i guess the kind of person that works at a library.", "answer": " it\u0092s not a library...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " so, dr. green, how\u0092s the old boat.", "answer": " they found rust. you know what rust does to a boat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " it gives it a nice antiquey look.", "answer": "  rust, is boat cancer, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " excuse me for a moment, will you please, i want to say good night to the levines, before we go.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " aw honey stop! it\u0092s not that bad.", "answer": " yeah.  op! uh-oh! i think your dad must\u0092ve added wrong. he only tipped like four percent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " yeah. that\u0092s daddy.", "answer": " that\u0092s daddy?! but doesn\u0092t it bother you? you\u0092re a waitress.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " yes, it bothers me ross, but y'know if he was a regular at the coffee house, i\u0092d be serving him sneezers.", "answer": " so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " so. ross, i\u0092ve bugged him about this a million times, he\u0092s not gonna change.", "answer": " you really serve people sneezers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " well um, i don\u0092t.", "answer": " you kids ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " thanks again, dr. green.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, i think i forgot my receipt.", "answer": " oh, ah, you don\u0092t need that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " the carbon, it\u0092s messy, i mean it gets on your fingers and causes, the, the ah, night blindness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  what is this? who put a twenty down here? huh?", "answer": " oh, yeah, that would be me, um, i have, i have a problem i-i tip way too much, way, way, too much, it\u0092s a sickness really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " yeah it is, it is.  we really, really have to do something about that.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " excuse me, you think i\u0092m cheap?", "answer": " oh daddy, no he didn\u0092t mean anything by that, he really didn\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " nothing i do means anything, really.", "answer": " this is nice. i pay two hundred dollars for dinner, you put down twenty, and you come out looking like mr. big shot. you really want to be mr. big shot? here, i\u0092ll tell you what, you pay the whole bill, mr. big shot, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " okay, some tricks of the trade. now, i\u0092ve never been able to cry as an actor, so if i\u0092m in a scene where i have to cry, i cut a hole in my pocket, take a pair of tweezers, and just start pulling. or ah, or, let\u0092s say i wanna convey that i\u0092ve just done something evil. that would be the basic \u0091i have a fishhook in my eyebrow and i like it\u0092  okay, let\u0092s say i\u0092ve just gotten bad news, well all i do there is try and divide 232 by 13.  and that\u0092s how it\u0092s done. great soap opera acting tonight everybody, class dismissed.", "answer": " hey, mr. trib.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey-hey.", "answer": " guess what, i got an audition!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " awww, one of my students got an audition. i\u0092m so proud.", "answer": " i was wondering if you would consider coaching me for it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " you bet! what\u0092s the part?", "answer": " oh it\u0092s great, it\u0092s a role on all my children, nick the boxer.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " you had to do it, didn\u0092t you? you couldn\u0092t just leave it alone.", "answer": " four percent. okay. i tip more than that when there\u0092s a bug in my food.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " ross, tonight was about the two of you getting along.  oh, would you just see my chiropractor, already.", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092m gonna go to a doctor who went to school in a mini-mall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey pheebs, what are you doing?", "answer": " i\u0092m, i\u0092m freaking out! monica kinda trusted me with something and she shouldn\u0092t have! all right, i haven\u0092t lived here in a while, so i have to ask you something. does monica still turn on the lights in her bedroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " um. yeah.", "answer": " i am soo dead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " all right, look, here\u0092s the bottom line ross, this is fixable, if we act fast, okay. so, i\u0092ll invite him to brunch tomorrow and you can make nice.", "answer": " look, honey, i have tried to make nice, it doesn\u0092t work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " okay, look, ross, i realise that my father is difficult, but that\u0092s why you have got to be the bigger man here.", "answer": " look sweetie, i could be the bigger man, i could be the biggest man, i could be a big, huge, giant man, and it still wouldn\u0092t make any difference, except that i could pick your father up and say \u0091like me! like me tiny doctor!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay, well can\u0092t you just try it one more time ross? for me? for me?", "answer": " rachel one brunch is not gonna solve anything. you gotta face it, okay we\u0092re never gonna get along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  what\u0092s this?", "answer": " isn\u0092t it cool! varoom! varoom!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " this is not the bed i ordered!", "answer": " i know, you must\u0092ve won like a contest or something!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " why is this car in my bedroom?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, okay, i-i wasn\u0092t looking, and the store says that they won\u0092t take it back because you signed for it...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " when did i sign for it?", "answer": " when i was you! y'know what, it\u0092s all joey\u0092s fault, \u0091cause he left his nose open!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " did you make brownies today?", "answer": " knock, knock.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  quick, take off your dress, he won\u0092t notice the bed.", "answer": " hey, i\u0092m going for sushi does anybody want..  whoa-whoa, somebody missed the off ramp.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it\u0092s monica\u0092s bed. what?", "answer": " okay.  it\u0092s a racecar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " so. this has always been monica\u0092s bed, what you\u0092re just noticing now, how self-involved are you?", "answer": " okay, well it this bed isn\u0092t new, how come there is plastic on the mattress?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " look, i just saw my best friends brains smeared across the canvas, that\u0092s not gonna be me, not me.", "answer": " wow! that was good. that was... tweezers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " whoa. that was really good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " you told him to play the boxer gay!!", "answer": " well, i-i might\u0092ve said supergay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " you totally screwed him over.", "answer": " joey, you\u0092re this guy\u0092s teacher. i mean how could you do this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " because, monica, the guy\u0092s so good, and i really, really want this part.", "answer": " well, if you really, really want it, then it\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  hi daddy.", "answer": " baby. ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " thanks for dinner last night.", "answer": " thank you for teaching me a valuable lesson.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " nice hair. what\u0092d ya do? swim here?", "answer": "  okay, that\u0092s it, i can\u0092t take it anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " what? what? he\u0092s interested in you. he-he likes your hair, he just wants to know how you got here.", "answer": " oh, please. sweetie it\u0092s hopeless, okay, i\u0092m just gonna go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " look, look i\u0092m sorry. it\u0092s just that....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " ross? what\u0092s with the neck?", "answer": " he\u0092s got this thing. and i keep telling him to go to my chiropractor...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " you\u0092re still going to that chiropractor, that man couldn\u0092t get into medical school in extapa!", "answer": " thank you! that\u0092s what i keep saying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " excuse me, dr. bobby happens to be an excellent doctor.", "answer": " uh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " wait a minute, his name is dr. bobby?", "answer": " well that\u0092s his last name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " and his first name.", "answer": " he\u0092s bobby bobby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " it\u0092s robert bobby.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " and um, excuse me, he helps me.", "answer": " oh-ho please. ask her how?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " what do you need help for?", "answer": " with my alignment. i\u0092ve got one leg shorter than the other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh god!", "answer": " argue with that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what? it\u0092s true, my right leg is two inches shorter.", "answer": " come on! you\u0092re just titling!  her legs are fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i know that!", "answer": " so, why do you let her go to a chiropractor for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry, let her?", "answer": " what can i do, she doesn\u0092t listen to me about renter\u0092s insurance either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " wait a minute, you don\u0092t have renter\u0092s insurance?!", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hey, would you ah, would you like some juice?", "answer": " i\u0092d love some juice. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay.  wow! this is going so well. did you see us? did you see?", "answer": " yeah honey, i\u0092m standing right there! why didn\u0092t you just tell him about the mole i haven\u0092t got checked yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " uh, may i help you?", "answer": " yeah, i talked to you on the phone, i\u0092m the lady that got stuck with the racecar bed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " look, it\u0092s like i told you, there\u0092s nothing i can do. you signed for it, monica velula geller.", "answer": " all right, jester man, look we wanna see the king.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " nobody sees the king!", "answer": " oh-ho-kay, i\u0092m talking to the king.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}]